

Changhun Lee

ROBOT ENGINEER · FIRMWARE SOFTWARE ENGINEE

Sanboncheon-ro 119-9, Gunpo-si, GyonugGi-do, 15816, Rep. of KOREA

□ (+82) 10-3659-8205 | Ich2895@naver.com | □ CH_Lee

"Hope for the world."

Summary.

I'm Changhun Lee, who want to become Robot Engineer. My research interests are wearable robot(Soft exoskelton, Hard exoskelton, etc.) for muscle strength and rehabilitation, HRI, Manipulator, Medical Robot, Control System and Firmware. I would like to help disabled people with my technology and make a world where everyone can be happy.

Research Interest_

Wearable Robot Soft & Hard Exoskelton

HRI Haptic

Medical Robot Surgery Robot & Manipulator

Education

KwangWoon University

Seoul, S.Korea

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022(Expected)

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

• Total GPA: 4.00/4.50 Major GPA: 4.12/4.50

STUDENT INTERN(ADVISOR DR. DONGHYUN HWANG)

• Club: BARAM(Robotics Academic Group) - [2020 Club president]

Work Experience __

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

• Research on HaptiCube.

- Research on Pose estimation with magnetic sensor
- · Participate in Smartfarm auto-driving system Project

Sunduck High school Seoul, S.Korea

TEACHERJun. 2020 - Sep. 2020

- Firmware Software Education(Arduino).
- 3D modeling Education.

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2019.12 **Finalist,** [17th] The World Embeded Software Contest 2019 Seoul, S.Korea

2020.08 **3rd Place**, Cham-bit Award *Kwangwoon univ.*

2020.08 **Top,** The first semester of the third grade Seoul, S.Korea

HONORS

2020.09 **Full tuition Scholarship**, For Top seat last semester Seoul, S.Korea

Skills____

Programming C/C++, Python, Matlab

Framework Solidworks, Catia

DevOps ROS

Languages Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity

Smart Factory with autocharge-scheduling

Seoul, S.Korea

May. 2019 - Dec. 2019

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

- 17th The World Embeded Software Contest 2019 project
- A system for efficiently operating a mobile robot used in a factory in consideration of the remaining battery, workload, etc.
- Modeling mobile robots, factory and Designing Close loop System to Control System
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**

Smart Walker[Cham-bit award]

Seoul, S.Korea

HARDWARE MODELING & DESIGN CLOSE LOOP CONTROL SYSTEM

Dec. 2019 - Oct. 2020

- Kwangwoon Univ.'s Cham-bit award project
- I wanted to prevent traffic accidents for the elderly..
- Walker to ensure the safety of the elderly people
- Regardless of the terrain, it speeds up at a constant speed.
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

Javis Seoul, S.Korea

Personal Project Aug. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- Mobile manipulator for helping disabled people
- To implement more diverse behaviors, The manipulator has 6DOF.
- To study ROS, all systems are implemented in ROS.
- The source code related to this project is on my **Github**

HaptiCube Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Aug. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- I implement simulations for interaction between HaptiCube and people.
- · Based on OpenGL, there is a version that utilizes Computer Vision and a version that is based on visual effects.
- The source code related to this project is on my Github

SmartFarm Seoul, S.Korea

KIST project Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- Creating a auto-driving robot to help Korean melon farm workers.
- All systems are implemented in ROS.
- To help farmers, we made a mobile robot with various functions.

Magnet Pose Estimation Seoul, S.Korea

KIST PROJECT Dec. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- We implement a magnet sensor system to follow the location of continuum mechanism
- We conducted a study to process and analyze Magnet's data and use it for Pose Estimation.

Publication

INTERNATIONAL

AIM2021, Development of an Embedded Sensor System for a 5-DOF Finger-wearable Tactile Interface, by Byeongkyu Lim, Changhun Lee, Donghyun Hwang

IEEE/ASME AIM

MARCH 16, 2021